this video will help to introduce the
该视频将有助于介绍
idea of Bayesian games which is a new
贝叶斯游戏的新思想
game representation so here I want to
游戏表示，所以我想在这里
think about auctions now canonically
现在考虑规范拍卖
when we think about auctions we think
当我们想到拍卖时，我们会想到
about something like this wood cutting
关于这种木头切割
from 1885 showing the auction of tea in
从1885年开始展示茶叶拍卖
Melbourne Australia we've got a guy in a
澳大利亚墨尔本，我们有一个家伙
top hat standing at the front of the
高顶礼帽站在前面
room and he's got a gavel in his hand
房间，他手里拿着木槌
and he's probably talking in a funny
而且他可能在讲有趣
voice and at some point he bangs the
声音，在某个时候，他砰的一声
gavel and somebody just won a bunch of
木槌和某人刚刚赢得了一堆
tea but auctions are a really practical
茶，但是拍卖真的很实用
thing they they really are quite
他们真的很
important in the world and they used for
在世界上很重要，他们曾经
a lot of different things here's an
很多不同的东西
example of a much more modern auction
现代拍卖的例子
this is an auction of bluefin tuna at a
这是蓝鳍金枪鱼的拍卖
fish market in Tokyo and you can see
东京的鱼市场，你可以看到
this is from 2008 and auctions are used
这是从2008年开始，使用拍卖
to sell fish because fish spoiled
卖鱼，因为鱼变质了
quickly and their value changes quickly
快速，他们的价值快速变化
and so it's important to find a way of
所以找到一种方法很重要
determining what the prices should be on
确定价格应该是多少
a day-by-day basis here's an auction by
每天的拍卖行
the US Marshal Service selling some
美国元帅处出售一些
horses that were seized by somebody who
被某人抓住的马
was convicted of embezzling money and so
因挪用金钱而被定罪，因此
the u.s. marshals got a bunch of guys
美国法警有很多人
and cowboy hats to round up this
和牛仔帽来凑合这个
person's horses and sell them off to
人的马，卖给
recover some of the embezzled money
追回一些挪用的钱
again you can see why an auction might
再次，您可以了解为什么拍卖会
be used here because the value of
在这里使用是因为
something like a horse is pretty unclear
像马一样的东西还不清楚
it depends on supply and demand it
这取决于供求关系
depends on intangible things like the
取决于像
value of the horse the number of other
马的价值其他
good horses on the market at a given
给定市场上的好马
time and so on here's yet another
时间等等，这是另一个
auction this is an auction of rugby
拍卖这是橄榄球的拍卖
players presumably only for a limited
大概只是有限的玩家
time and again you can see why an
一次又一次，您可以看到为什么
auction might need to be used because
可能需要使用拍卖，因为
it's pretty unclear what this guy would
目前还不清楚这个家伙会做什么
be worth of course not all auctions
当然值得所有拍卖
happen in person here's a famous auction
亲自发生，这是著名的拍卖
that occurred on eBay a few years ago
几年前发生在eBay上
this was a situation where a woman in
在这种情况下，
Florida was eating a grilled cheese
佛罗里达正在吃烤奶酪
sandwich that she had made for
她做的三明治
you can see a picture of it right here
你可以在这里看到它的图片
and she took a bite out of it and then
她咬了一口，然后
she was amazed to discover what she
她惊讶地发现了自己的东西
considered to be a perfect likeness of
被认为是完美的肖像
the Virgin Mary in the the shape of the
圣母玛利亚的形状
burn mark on the grilled cheese sandwich
烤奶酪三明治上有烫痕
right there and so she was so amazed she
就在那里，所以她很惊讶
decided that this was a religious relic
认为这是宗教遗物
she stopped eating the sandwich and like
她停止吃三明治，喜欢
anyone would do if they discovered a
任何人只要发现一个
sign from God
来自上帝的迹象
she posted it on eBay to sell to the
她将其发布在eBay上以出售给
highest bidder this is kind of
出价最高的人
interesting both because it's ridiculous
都有趣，因为这太荒谬了
but also because it goes to show how the
而且还因为它显示了
Internet allows auctions to create
互联网允许拍卖创造
markets in places where they really
他们真正去过的地方的市场
wouldn't have existed before so if this
以前不存在，所以如果这
had happened before the internet it
发生在互联网之前
seems pretty clear that this woman would
似乎很清楚，这个女人会
have had a hard time finding a buyer for
很难找到买家
her grilled cheese sandwich but you can
她的烤奶酪三明治，但你可以
see that when I took this screenshot the
看到当我拍摄此屏幕截图时，
auction still had almost four days to go
拍卖还有将近四天的时间
and already the top bid was seven
最高出价已经是七个
thousand six hundred US dollars and this
一千六百美元，这
this really was not a hoax this was an
这真的不是骗局，这是
actual auction it was covered in the
实际拍卖中
news so that's that's kind of an amazing
新闻，那真是太神奇了
thing it goes to show the power of
它显示出力量的东西
auctions to to match up buyers and
拍卖以匹配买家
sellers here's the last auction picture
卖家这是最近一次拍卖的照片
I want to show you this is what's called
我想告诉你这就是所谓的
a silent auction in a charity auction so
慈善拍卖中的无声拍卖，所以
what's going on here is there there are
这是怎么回事
actually two different bundles for sale
实际上是两个不同的捆绑销售
so there's a gift basket here for sale
所以这里有一个礼物篮要出售
and all of the people who are interested
和所有感兴趣的人
in buying it are able to go up and
在购买它能够上升，
inspect it decide what they think it's
检查它决定他们认为是什么
worth to them and then they write a bid
对他们来说很有价值，然后他们写了一个报价
they write their name and an amount that
他们写下自己的名字和金额
they're willing to pay on this sheet of
他们愿意为此支付
paper here and the reason that I think
本文在这里以及我认为的原因
the silent auction is particularly
无声拍卖尤其如此
interesting is we can really see how
有趣的是我们真的可以看到
this might look like a game we here have
这看起来像我们这里的游戏
a well-defined action space you come you
一个定义明确的动作空间，您来了
you look at the piece of paper you can
你看着那张纸，你可以
see the moves of the players who have
看到有
moved before you and then you
在你之前移动，然后你
in action which is choosing to write
在选择写作的行动中
down a number and at the end presumably
减少一个数字，最后大概
you don't write down a number that is
你不会写下一个数字
worth more than the gift basket is worth
价值超过礼品篮的价值
to you at the end if you have the
最后，如果您有
highest number you win the gift basket
您赢得礼品篮的最高号码
you realize an amount of utility which
您意识到一定数量的效用
is which depends on how good the gift
取决于礼物的好坏
basket is from your point of view and
从您的角度来看篮子
you pay whatever amount it is that you
您支付的金额是
wrote down on the piece of paper which
在那张纸上写下
is presumably less and you get the
大概更少，你得到
difference as your utility for having
与您拥有的实用程序不同
played the game so all of this looks
玩了游戏，所以所有这些看起来
like something we can really model in
就像我们可以真正建模的东西
the context of this course and if we
本课程的背景，如果我们
realize we can model the silent auction
意识到我们可以为无声拍卖建模
this way we can probably see that we can
这样，我们可能会看到，我们可以
model the other options that I've just
模拟我刚才的其他选项
described in this sort of way as well
也用这种方式描述
however there's something really
但是确实有一些东西
critical about the case of the silent
对沉默的情况至关重要
auction which is different from the
拍卖与
games that we've talked about in this
我们在此讨论的游戏
course already and that is that when I
当然，那就是当我
want to reason about what other people
想知道其他人
will do in this game I need to think
在这个游戏中我会想
about what they think the gift basket is
他们认为礼物篮是什么
worth to them that's going to be
对他们来说值得
something very important to the way they
对他们的方式非常重要的事情
choose to act in the game and critically
选择在游戏中扮演重要角色
this is something that will affect their
这会影响他们的
utility and it's not something that I
实用程序，这不是我的事
know and so this is a case where I'm not
知道，所以这是我不知道的情况
quite sure what other players utility
非常确定其他玩家的实用程序
functions are even in cases where I can
功能甚至在我可以的情况下
imagine what all of the actions taken in
想象所有采取的行动
the game are so this is a different sort
游戏是不同的
of setting than we've ever looked at
设置比我们以前看过的
before and hopefully you can see that
以前，希望你能看到
this is really necessary to model the
这对于建模
case of auctions it's really fundamental
拍卖的情况真的很重要
to an auction that I'm not quite sure
参加我不太确定的拍卖
what the good is worth to all of the
什么对所有的人都有价值
other participants in the auction and
拍卖的其他参与者
that fact is really critical to my
这个事实对我来说真的很关键
strategic reasoning and the option so
战略推理及其选择
Bayesian games are a formalism that
贝叶斯游戏是形式主义，
allows us to model this kind of
允许我们建模这种
uncertainty uncertainty about the
不确定性
utility functions and this week we'll go
实用程序功能，本周我们将去
into Bayesian games in more detail
更详细地介绍贝叶斯游戏